[{"question":" What type of relationship is defined as one resource existing only if another parent resource exist-for example, pages in a book?","options":[{"text":"`Partial`","correct":true},{"text":"`dependent`","correct":false},{"text":"`associative`","correct":false},{"text":"`linked`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which URL pattern s recommended when working with one resource and a collection of resources?","options":[{"text":"`/companies/{id} and/company`","correct":false},{"text":"`/company/{id} and/companies`","correct":false},{"text":"`/companies/{id} and/companies`","correct":true},{"text":"`/company/{id} and/company`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" When dealing with JSON web Tokens (JWTs), what is a claim?","options":[{"text":"`data in the token`","correct":true},{"text":"`Ownership`","correct":false},{"text":"`a permission`","correct":false},{"text":"`and integer`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which REST contraint specifies that knowledge and understanding obtained from one component of the API should be generally applicable elsewhere in the API?","options":[{"text":"`Uniform Interface`","correct":true},{"text":"`Client-Server`","correct":false},{"text":"`Stateless`","correct":false},{"text":"`Chacheable`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What would you enable to allow a browser on another site to make an AJAX request to your API?","options":[{"text":"`HTTP`","correct":false},{"text":"`REST`","correct":false},{"text":"`OPTIONS`","correct":false},{"text":"`CORS`","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" APIs commonly use webhooks to `**\\*\\*\\*\\***\\_\\_\\_\\_**\\*\\*\\*\\***`.","options":[{"text":"`notify other systems of an event`","correct":true},{"text":"`catch error faster`","correct":false},{"text":"`improve error logging`","correct":false},{"text":"`log additional data`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is the underlying goal of all APIs?","options":[{"text":"`to add new technologies to an organization's infrastructure.`","correct":false},{"text":"`to share features and functionality with other system.`","correct":true},{"text":"`to move infrastructure to the cloud.`","correct":false},{"text":"`to appease the latest digital transformation effort.`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" Which is a common command-line tool for using or exploring an API?","options":[{"text":"`bash`","correct":false},{"text":"`curl`","correct":true},{"text":"`ssh`","correct":false},{"text":"`powerShell`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":" What is the modern specification for describing an API?","options":[{"text":"`OpenAPI (Swagger)`","correct":true},{"text":"`WADL`","correct":false},{"text":"`WSDL`","correct":false},{"text":"`OAuth`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which HTTP verb is normally used to update or create a resource in an API?","options":[{"text":"`SUBMIT`","correct":false},{"text":"`WRITE`","correct":false},{"text":"`POST`","correct":true},{"text":"`CREATE`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is one benefit of server-side caching in APIs?","options":[{"text":"`Mobile app work better.`","correct":false},{"text":"`It improves uptime.`","correct":false},{"text":"`It offers better security.`","correct":false},{"text":"`It reduce load on servers.`","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Your API resource does no allow deletion, and a client application attempted to delete the resource. What HTTP respose code should you return?","options":[{"text":"`409 Conflict`","correct":false},{"text":"`400 Bad Request`","correct":false},{"text":"`406 Not Acceptable`","correct":false},{"text":"`405 Method Not Allowed`","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is OpenID Connect?","options":[{"text":"`an identify layer on top of OAuth 2.0`","correct":true},{"text":"`the new name for SAML 3.0`","correct":false},{"text":"`a modern replacement for API keys`","correct":false},{"text":"`an SSO competitor for OAuth 2.0`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is one benefit of GraphQl over REST approaches?","options":[{"text":"`flexible querying/responses`","correct":true},{"text":"`more stable APIs`","correct":false},{"text":"`compatible with more gateways`","correct":false},{"text":"`more secure by default`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which REST constraint specifies that there should be no shared context?","options":[{"text":"`Stateless`","correct":true},{"text":"`Client-Server`","correct":false},{"text":"`Uniform Interface`","correct":false},{"text":"`Cacheable`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What purpose does a User-Agent serve?","options":[{"text":"`It identifies the user ID.`","correct":false},{"text":"`It identifies the client application or SDK.`","correct":true},{"text":"`It identifies if the API should expect a user authentication.`","correct":false},{"text":"`It identifies if the API should accept microservice traffic.`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". If you were to add versioning by using the Accept and Content-Type header, what would be the correct format of the header value?","options":[{"text":"`application/json`","correct":false},{"text":"`application/json_version2`","correct":false},{"text":"`text/html`","correct":true},{"text":"`application/vnd.myapp.v2+json`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is one benefit that OAuth provides over an API key approach?","options":[{"text":"`A token is encrypted.`","correct":false},{"text":"`A token is encoded.`","correct":false},{"text":"`A token is scoped to the use case.`","correct":true},{"text":"`A token can be shared between systems.`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". The ability to execute the same API request over and over again without changing the resource's state is an example of \\_\\_\\_.","options":[{"text":"`stateless architecture`","correct":false},{"text":"`idempotency`","correct":true},{"text":"`a uniform interface`","correct":false},{"text":"`cacheability`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What component can you use to wrap legacy architectures or protocols into a REST interface for easier consumption and integration?","options":[{"text":"`API proxy`","correct":true},{"text":"`API gateway`","correct":false},{"text":"`OpenAPI`","correct":false},{"text":"`OAuth authorization server`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What protection does a JSON Web Token (JWT) offer to mitigate tampering with its contents?","options":[{"text":"`transport over SSL`","correct":false},{"text":"`encrypted payload`","correct":false},{"text":"`a signature`","correct":true},{"text":"`encoded payload`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What OAuth term is used to represent permissions?","options":[{"text":"`token`","correct":false},{"text":"`scope`","correct":true},{"text":"`claim`","correct":false},{"text":"`back channel`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What additional type of token would you see when using OpenID Connect?","options":[{"text":"`ID token`","correct":true},{"text":"`refresh token`","correct":false},{"text":"`access token`","correct":false},{"text":"`auth code token`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What should you add to a Cache-Control response header to specify that a response should not be stored in an intermediary cache?","options":[{"text":"`no-proxy`","correct":false},{"text":"`client-only`","correct":false},{"text":"`restricted`","correct":false},{"text":"`private`","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which OAuth grant type can support a refresh token?","options":[{"text":"`Authorization Code Grant`","correct":false},{"text":"`Client Credentials Grant`","correct":true},{"text":"`Implicit Grant`","correct":false},{"text":"`Authentication Grant`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Using OAuth, what scope would you request for write access to the API?","options":[{"text":"`It varies from API to API.`","correct":false},{"text":"`admin`","correct":true},{"text":"`write`","correct":false},{"text":"`read-write`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which property would you use to include subresources directly into a JSON document?","options":[{"text":"`\\_embedded`","correct":false},{"text":"`resources`","correct":false},{"text":"`subresources`","correct":true},{"text":"`\\_links`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the best way to track SDK and version usage?","options":[{"text":"`tracking downloads`","correct":true},{"text":"`Accept headers`","correct":false},{"text":"`user agents`","correct":false},{"text":"`polling users`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which REST constraint allows for the presence of caching, routing, and other systems between the client and server?","options":[{"text":"`Layered System`","correct":false},{"text":"`Stateless`","correct":false},{"text":"`Client-Server`","correct":true},{"text":"`Cacheable`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which content is best to include in your documentation?","options":[{"text":"`your tech stack`","correct":false},{"text":"`reasoning for your naming schema`","correct":false},{"text":"`your mission statement`","correct":false},{"text":"`sample code`","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What metric tracks overall availability for your API?","options":[{"text":"`Response Time`","correct":false},{"text":"`Time to First Hello World`","correct":false},{"text":"`TTL`","correct":false},{"text":"`Uptime`","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the recommended method and URL pattern for retrieving a specific user?","options":[{"text":"`GET /user/{id}`","correct":false},{"text":"`GET /users/{id}`","correct":true},{"text":"`GET /user?id={id}`","correct":false},{"text":"`GET /users?id={id}`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the purpose of a link relation?","options":[{"text":"`to describe relationships between resources or actions`","correct":false},{"text":"`to describe subresources related to the current one`","correct":false},{"text":"`to link two resources together`","correct":true},{"text":"`to describe a resource and its purpose`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". When building SDKs, which languages should you support?","options":[{"text":"Java, Javascript, and .NET","correct":false},{"text":"and you can support","correct":false},{"text":"PHP, Python, and Go","correct":false},{"text":"the languages that your target users use","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which property would you use to include references to other resources in a JSON document?","options":[{"text":"resources","correct":true},{"text":"\\_embedded","correct":false},{"text":"subresources","correct":false},{"text":"\\_links","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is OAuth?","options":[{"text":"an authorization framework for granted delegated access","correct":true},{"text":"an approach to single sign-on for APIs","correct":false},{"text":"a method for API authentication","correct":false},{"text":"HTTP Basic Authentication 2.0","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What should your API documentation describe?","options":[{"text":"JSON","correct":false},{"text":"HTTP","correct":false},{"text":"common use cases","correct":true},{"text":"your tech stack","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the purpose of an OAuth refresh token?","options":[{"text":"to share user profile information","correct":false},{"text":"to update an API configuration","correct":false},{"text":"to keep a web session active","correct":false},{"text":"to retrieve an access token","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is Time to First Hello World?","options":[{"text":"how long it takes for a developer to do something with your API","correct":true},{"text":"how long it takes to start a new programming language","correct":false},{"text":"how long it takes to install your SDK","correct":false},{"text":"how long it takes to read your documentation","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which response header tells the client and intermediaries that the response is not to be cached anywhere?","options":[{"text":"Cache-State: none","correct":false},{"text":"Expires:-1","correct":false},{"text":"Cache-Control: no-cache","correct":false},{"text":"Cache-Control: no-store","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What component hides the distinctions or boundaries between various microservices from end-client applications?","options":[{"text":"`API gateway`","correct":true},{"text":"`API logging `","correct":false},{"text":"`a layered system `","correct":false},{"text":"`API proxy`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". The textbook approach to api versioning is to use **\\_**.","options":[{"text":"`common knowledge`","correct":false},{"text":"`URLs`","correct":false},{"text":"`no versioning`","correct":false},{"text":"`the Accept header`","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which is the most secure method to transmit an API key?","options":[{"text":"`URL parameter`","correct":false},{"text":"`Authorization header`","correct":true},{"text":"`Base64 encoding`","correct":false},{"text":"`Basic Auth`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Within Oauth, what component validates the user's identity?","options":[{"text":"`client`","correct":false},{"text":"`not specified`","correct":false},{"text":"`authorization server`","correct":true},{"text":"`resource server`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". API traffic that is entirely internal to your organisation is normally called \\_\\_\\_\\_?","options":[{"text":"`inbound traffic`","correct":false},{"text":"`north-south traffic `","correct":false},{"text":"`internal traffic `","correct":true},{"text":"`east-west traffic`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the best approach for requesting JSON instead of XML from an API?","options":[{"text":"`Add .json to the URL.`","correct":false},{"text":"`APIs do not use XML.`","correct":false},{"text":"`Use the Content-Type header.`","correct":false},{"text":"`Use the Accept header.`","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". When a user attempts to access a record that is not their own, whitch HTTP response code is the most appropriate?","options":[{"text":"`403`","correct":false},{"text":"`404`","correct":false},{"text":"`401`","correct":true},{"text":"`405`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which is a benefit of using an API gateway?","options":[{"text":"`HTTP verbs`","correct":false},{"text":"`JSON payloads`","correct":false},{"text":"`HTTP response codes`","correct":false},{"text":"`rate limiting/throttling`","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". API testing must be treated as **\\_\\_**?","options":[{"text":"`red team testing`","correct":false},{"text":"`white box testing`","correct":false},{"text":"`blue box testing`","correct":false},{"text":"`black box testing`","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which HTTP verb is used in a CORS preflight request?","options":[{"text":"`PUT`","correct":false},{"text":"`POST`","correct":false},{"text":"`GET`","correct":false},{"text":"`OPTIONS`","correct":true}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which response header will tell the client that the response is cached for 1 minute ?","options":[{"text":"`Expires: 1 minute`","correct":false},{"text":"`Cache-Control: max-age=60`","correct":true},{"text":"`Expires: 1 January 2020`","correct":false},{"text":"`Cache-Expires: max-age=60`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". What is the concept that allows an API client to explore an API via links embedded in payloads?","options":[{"text":"`hypermedia`","correct":false},{"text":"`link relations`","correct":true},{"text":"`parsing`","correct":false},{"text":"`browsing`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""},{"question":". Which HTTP response code describes a new resource as created successfully?","options":[{"text":"`200`","correct":false},{"text":"`201`","correct":true},{"text":"`204`","correct":false},{"text":"`202`","correct":false}],"illustrator":""}]